老爸有招 第一季第十二集
本字幕由深影字幕组原创翻译
翻译  尼采  慕斯少女
翻译  Brush  守护毛毛
校对  shy哥滔
压制  北岛
匹兹堡最受欢迎的
伯恩斯兄弟工程公司
看看谁从地板展览会上回来了
Look who's back from the flooring expo.
这次你又顺走了多少个
How many free burritos
免费的墨西哥卷饼啊
did you sneak out with this time?
六个
Six.
一整天都得和你待在这个
I'm so happy I'll be sealed
密不透风的地方 我真是太开心了
inside this tin can with you all day.
我们的命运或许被我改写了
I think I might have just changed our lives.
我发现 比我更钟爱免费墨西哥卷饼的人
Turns out the only person who likes free burritos
只有丽莎·麦卡弗里了
more than me is Lisa McCaffrey.
那个地产开发商吗
The property developer?
几年前我就想和她见面谈谈了
I've been trying to get a meeting with her for years.
我在调料区和她聊了几句
Well, I chatted her up at the salsa bar,
还在她往卷饼里加鳄梨酱的时候帮她端了碟子
and then I held her plate while she guac'ed her taco.
你是不是在暗示我
Is that your way of telling me
我要被她起诉了
I'm gonna get a call from her lawyer?
不会 我先发制人
No, I broke the ice.
为我们赢得了他们新开发项目的投标机会
And I got us a chance to bid on their new development.
五幢房子
Five houses.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
唐 我们从来没有做过这么大的项目
Don, we've never done a job that big before.
这可是一大笔收入啊
That could mean a lot of money coming in.
我们可以买更多设备 雇更多员工
We could buy more equipment, hire more crew.
我觉得这次我们的赢面不小
I think we've got a real shot at this.
我使出了浑身解数
I gave her the full Don Burns.
她被我惊艳得头发飞舞 就跟拍MV似的
Her hair was blowing back like a girl in a music video.
好了 所以
Okay, so
我们和丽莎面谈的时候
when we sit down with Lisa,
我会先亮出成功案例
I'll hit her with our glowing references,
过一遍数据
run her through the numbers.
然后我施展魅力 最后 以一个笑话收尾
Then I turn on the charm, and, boom, close with a joke.
好
Okay.
是不是要拿独腿芭蕾女舞者艾琳开玩笑
You gonna do the one about the one-legged ballerina names Eileen?
不 麦卡弗里是爱尔兰人
No. McCaffrey's Irish.
我要讲教皇卡在电话亭里的那个
I'm gonna go with the Pope stuck in the phone booth.
这种社会舆论她会喜欢的
She'll enjoy the social commentary.
好的 然后你把我们的浮标钥匙链发给他们
Okay, then you hand out our floating key chains,
这次尽量不要
and try not to give 'em the one
把挂着自己车钥匙的那个也给他们
with your car keys attached this time.
然后 就... 就好了
And then, boom, we... we're done.
推介准备得怎么样了
Hey, how's the pitch coming?
看上去不错 我们完事儿
Looking good, yeah. We're all done.
要看比赛了
We're gonna watch the game.
你觉得今晚请洛厄尔过来
how would you feel about inviting Lowell
和你们一起看怎么样
to come watch with you tonight?
洛厄尔
Lowell?
来这里
Here?
邀请他
On purpose?
我在学校里看够他了
I see enough of him at school.
而且在昨天"带爸爸去上学"活动上
And he was in rare form yesterday
他的表现跟他平时差远了
at "Bring Your Dad to School" day.
作为一个建筑承包商
So, as a contractor, I get to use
我能够使用很多很酷的工具
a lot of really cool tools,
比如这把激光测温枪
like this thermal laser,
它可以告诉我任何东西的温度
which can tell me the temperature of anything.
罗德里格兹老师是...
Mrs. Rodriguez is...
冷若冰霜 一如既往
ice-cold, as usual.
现在艾米会给每一个人发
Okay, now Emme is gonna hand out free
我们的免费浮标钥匙链
floating key chains to all of you.
谢谢你 伯恩斯先生 给孩子们发这些
Thank you, Mr. Burns, for giving the kids things
他们以后能用来砸我了
they will throw at me later.
洛厄尔 到你了
Lowell, you're up.
谢谢 罗德里格兹老师
Thanks, Mrs. Rodriguez.
我叫洛厄尔
My name is Lowell,
我是一个全职爸爸
and I am a stay-at-home dad,
也就是说 一周有四十个小时
which means 40 hours a week,
我都是一个人独处
I am entirely alone.
这也使我发现了我的才能
And that's how I discovered my talent
就是把吐司啃出各个州的形状
for eating toast into the shapes of states.
所以我才觉得你应该邀请他
Well, that's why I think you should invite him.
今天我在杂货店看到他了
I saw him at the grocery store today,
一眼就看到他孤零零的
and he was obviously lonely.
他不是唐和我会找来一起玩的那种人
He's just not the kind of guy that Don and I hang out with.
有那么糟糕吗
Well, I mean, is that such a bad thing?
唐 你挺讨我喜欢的
I mean, Don, you know, I love you,
但当你们俩在一起的时候 你有一半的话是以
but when you two are together, half your sentences end with,
"她也这么说"结尾
"That's what she said."
就算那个女生说不出这种话来
Even when there's no way that's what she could have said.
亲爱的 你可以试着不要插手吗
Honey, could you just try to keep your fingers out of it.
她也这么说
That's what she said.
我已经告诉洛厄尔他可以过来了
Yeah, well, I already told Lowell he could come over.
他会在十分钟后到
He'll be here in ten minutes.
什么 所以你就背着我
What? So basically you just
给我找了个玩伴
set me up on a playdate?
男人可不是这么交朋友的
That is not how men make friends.
我是要让你长长见识
I am expanding your horizons.
我自己也这么做
I do it for myself, too,
所以明天我约了艾丽西亚·罗德里格兹
which is why tomorrow I am going for drinks
喝点东西
with Alicia Rodriguez.
想不到你会对自己做出这种事
Wow, I can't believe you're doing that to yourself.
她也这么说
That's what she said.
我是个女人 我知道她说了什么
I am a woman. I know what she said.
- 你们好啊 - 嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
非常感谢你们邀请我
Thanks so much for having me.
安迪说你想请我过来看比赛
When Andi said you wanted me to come watch the game,
把我高兴坏了
I was super jazzed.
同乐同乐
Well, the jazz is mutual.
但有件事 洛厄尔
But here's the thing, Lowell.
企鹅队的比赛一开始 我们就不怎么讲话了
Once the Penguins game starts, we don't talk much.
我从来不在比赛期间讲话... 兆头不好
Oh, I never talk during Pens games... bad luck.
得在开球前
Gotta unpack these snacks
把零食都拿出来
before the puck drops.
首先 七层蘸酱
First up, seven-layer dip.
先告诉你们 最底下一层是玉米片哟
Spoiler alert, the bottom layer is Doritos.
你说什么
What did you just say?
他说 玉米片蘸酱
He said Dorito dip.
就是说 你可以用更多的玉米片
That's dip with Doritos
蘸这个含有玉米片的蘸酱
in it that you can dip into with more Doritos?
这是你发明的
You invented this?
我这辈子可算等到你了
I've been waiting for you my whole life.
怎么样了 三位
How's it going, fellas?
不许说话 比赛要开始了
No talking. The game's starting.
抱歉
Sorry.
我也等了你一辈子了
I've been waiting for you my whole life.
这是中场休息点心
Here's an intermission treat.
新鲜出炉的爆米花
Fresh popcorn with Junior Mints
搀薄荷糖
already mixed in.
不是吧
Shut up!
唐 我刚收到了一封邮件
Hey, Don, I just got an e-mail
丽莎·麦卡弗里的人发的
from Lisa McCaffrey's people.
他们问我们做展示有何设备需求
They want to know our tech needs for the presentation.
准备一桶水放钥匙链就行啦
A bucket of water for the key chain would help.
能让他们看到钥匙链浮起来
They could see it float.
这算个点子
Okay, that's an idea.
但他们的设备需求应该不是这个意思
But I don't think that's what they meant by "tech" needs.
他们只是想知道你的电脑里有没有幻灯片
They just want to know if your PowerPoint is on your laptop,
或者要不要连接他们的显示器
or if you're gonna integrate with their monitors.
用的是数字信号 模拟信号
Do you need HDMI, VGA,
或者直接用复合视频信号
or are you going straight composite?
这些信号都是啥
H-G-D... what?
都是技术上的东西
It's pretty technical.
有孩子以前 我是做销售的
I only know about it because I used to work in marketing
所以有些了解
before we had kids, and I lost
另外我跟老婆扳手腕 输了的人带孩子
a very high-stakes arm wrestle to my wife.
- 你以前做过销售 - 没错
- Y-you were in marketing?  - Mm-hmm.
你介意帮我们完成展示吗
Oh, hey, would you mind if we ran our presentation by you?
等等 打住
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 怎么 - 我才是管销售的
- What? - I'm our marketing guy.
让小黛比操心零食就好了
Let Little Debbie here take care of the snacks.
但小黛比听起来很懂行
Yeah, but Little Debbie sounds like he knows what he's doing.
我很喜欢昵称
Okay, I like that we have nicknames,
但更希望你们能考虑一下"冠军"或"童子军"
but maybe we could try something like "Champ" or "Scout".
我不想到那以后跟个外行一样
I don't want to go in there and look like amateurs.
我们不需要那些东西
Well, I'm just saying, I don't think we need all that stuff.
但我们在面对一个新局面
Well, I'm just saying this is a whole new ball game.
洛厄尔 告诉我几个高科技名词
Lowell, back me up with some of your nerd words there.
来呗 小童子军 说吧
Come on, Scout, speak up.
我很喜欢这个名字 谢谢
Well, I loved that. Thank you.
总的来说 这些大公司听推介报告时
Um, generally, when these big companies hear pitches,
希望看到多媒体化的展示
they're expecting a multimedia presentation.
动画制作 3D模型都可以
Animation, 3D models.
有需要 我可以帮助你们
And I'd be happy to help if you want.
- 太好了 - 不 谢谢
- That sounds great. - No, thanks.
你为什么要反对
Why are you getting your back up?
因为这会议是我争取的 最后也是我来拍板
Because I got the meeting, and I'll close the deal.
一直以来都是如此
It's what I've done since we started.
现在 先失陪了
Now, if you'll excuse me,
蘸酱搞得我肚子疼
this dip has upset my stomach,
我想回家休息了
and I would like to be at home.
如果它让你不舒服 你为什么还要带走
Well, if it made you sick, why are you taking it with you?
等我好点了再吃
So later, when I feel better,
就能知道是不是它的问题
I can eat it again and make sure that's what it was.
今晚跟洛厄尔相处得怎么样
How'd it go tonight with Lowell?
他还不错 唐有点问题
Uh, he was fine. Don was the problem.
他是不是吃多零食
Did he eat too many snacks
又拉肚子了
and have to take his pants off again?
不 不是
No, no, no, no.
洛厄尔说要帮我们做一个高科技的推介
Lowell offered to help us make a more high-tech pitch,
可把唐惹毛了
and Don got all bent out of shape.
他裤链都开了
His fly was down,
但我觉得那只是意外
but I think it was just a coincidence.
不算意外
Well, it's not a surprise.
唐从来都不爱学新东西
I mean, Don is not a huge fan of knowledge.
还记得我们给他每日一词日历时
Remember how mad he got when we gave him
- 他怒火中烧 - 没错
- that word-of-the-day calendar?  - Yeah.
他有一个理论
Yeah, he's got this theory
认为他的脑子和胃一样
that his brain is like his stomach.
进去一些新的
Every new thing he takes in
就会挤出来一些旧的
pushes an old thing out.
我必须给唐的脑子腾出空间
I've got to make room in Don's brain
放洛厄尔的点子
for Lowell's ideas.
好吧...
Well...
我很高兴看到你和洛厄尔相处不错
I'm just excited that you got along with Lowell.
你有没有告诉他今天相处很愉快
Did you tell him how much fun you had hanging out with him?
男人从来不这么做
Men don't do stuff like that.
洛厄尔发来的
It's from Lowell.
"和你一起玩感觉真不错"
"I had so much fun hanging out with you."
笑脸☻ 流星🌠 冰球
Smiley face, shooting star, hockey puck.
你必须给他回信息 说点好听的
You have to e-mail him back. Something thoughtful.
你能不能别再逼我
Will you stop trying to make me do
和另一个男人做奇怪的事
weird things with other men?
她也这么说
That's what she said.
拜托 这确实是那个梗
Come on, that was solid.
我确实应该回信息
But I should write Lowell back.
他提出要帮忙
He is offering to help me.
要不你来
Uh, well, you do it.
我不擅长这些
I'm bad at these.
说一点既随意又爷们的话
Just say something breezy, yet manly.
有趣
Oh, fun.
"和你一起玩很开心
Okay, "Great hanging out with you, too.
"你的裤子超级可爱...
"Your pants were super cute...
好基友"
bro."
有意思
Very funny.
你已经发送了吗
Did you actually send that?
快撤回
Get it back.
太晚了
It's too late.
你有个新男朋友了
You have a new boyfriend.
好了 小豆丁
Okay, Butterbean,
乖乖上学好吗 亲一个
Have a great day, huh? Mwah.
对了 你的零食
Oh, listen, for your snack,
我放了爆米花和薄荷糖
I gave you popcorn with Junior Mints.
真的吗
Shut... up.
我就知道你会喜欢
I know, you're gonna love it.
亚当 亚当
Adam! Adam!
嘿 洛厄尔
Hey, Lowell.
早上好 "基友"
Good morning, "bro."
你看到我的短信了
Ah, so you got my e-mail.
我太激动了 我做了一个动画
I was so pumped, I made an animated graphic
是关于你们公司的商标的
of the Burns Brothers logo to show you what I was
昨天晚上提到过 看看吧
talking about last night... take a look.
我的天 我们的名字在房子外面炸开了
Wow, our names exploded right out of that house.
你能发给我吗 这样我就能给唐看了
Hey, can you send that to me so I can show it to Don?
他会喜欢的
I think he'll really love it.
早就发了 已发送
Already did. Already sent it.
这只是个开头
This is only the beginning.
我要让你爱上我的演示报告
I can make a presentation that you'll like even more
比我的裤子更爱哦
than my super cute pants.
你的语气在短信里不太一样
You know, your tone is very different in e-mails.
是的 活脱脱我老婆的口吻
Yeah, people say I sound just like my wife.
安迪发的短信 是吗
It was Andi, wasn't it?
- 实话说...- 别回答了
- Well, to be honest... - Don't answer.
让我继续高兴下去
I just want to ride this rainbow.
我的天 我们的名字在房子外面炸开了
Wow! Our names just exploded out of that house!
做得不错 我喜欢
Nice job. I love it.
不是我做的 是洛厄尔
I didn't make it, Lowell did.
什么破玩意
I hate it.
你到底怎么回事
What is your problem?
这是我和你的生意
Our business is just you and me.
我负责招徕生意 你反正就做些那啥
I'm the sales guy, and you do whatever you do.
建筑
The work?
我就是觉得三这数字不吉利
I'm just saying three's a bad number.
肯定有人被挤出去
Somebody's gonna get pushed out,
我不喜欢这样
and I don't like it.
你总是担心被挤出去
You're always worried about something getting pushed out.
又不是所有的东西都跟你肚子一样 唐
Not everything is like your stomach, Don.
我真的觉得应该让洛厄尔帮我们
I really think we should let Lowell help us.
我不准
Well, I forbid it.
我们是合作伙伴 你不能直接不准
You can't forbid it, we're partners.
好 投票表决
Fine, let's take a vote.
我们之前试过
We've tried this before.
只有我们俩 永远都不行
There's only two of us. It never works.
行不行试试看
Well, let's just see what happens.
赞同的举手
All in favor?
反对的举手
All opposed?
我都不知道我为什么要配合
I don't know why I even do it.
你在学校和亚当处得怎么样
So, um, how's it going at school with Adam?
还好 还好
I, uh, it's f-fine. Fine.
你们又闹矛盾了
Aw, did you guys have another fight?
恰恰相反
On the contrary.
跟你说 算了 其实也...
Um, uh, y-you know what, never mind. It's...
求你了 说嘛
Ah, come on. Spill it.
你不说我是不会罢休的
I'm not gonna drop it until you tell me.
你不会有意见吧
You won't judge?
我就是有也不让你看出来 怎么样
You won't know if I do, how about that?
昨天晚上
Last night,
我做了一个关于你老公的梦
I had a dream about your husband.
有点
It was...
不可描述
Cinemax-y.
亚当和我
And Adam and I were,
你懂的 啪啪啪
you know, boom-chucka-chucka.
还有音效
And sound effects.
想不到你竟然把整个演示都做好了
Wow. I can't believe you got the whole presentation done.
你是怎么做到让一只秃鹰站到我肩膀上的
And how did you get a bald eagle to land on my shoulder?
首先就是要有信心
The first thing I did was believe it was possible.
你确定唐没问题吗
Hey, are you sure Don's gonna be okay with this?
他要是看到这个 他肯定激动得不得了
Oh, when he sees this, he is gonna be more than okay with it.
让我来负责搞定唐 好吗
You know what, let me worry about Don, okay?
我们再看一遍
Let's watch it again.
洛厄尔在这干什么
What is Lowell doing here?
唐 我还以为你今晚要上班卓琴课呢
Don, I thought you had a banjo lesson tonight.
我老师去船上表演去了
My teacher got a gig on a riverboat.
正好你回来了
Well, hey, I'm glad you're here.
快来看看洛厄尔的演示
Check out Lowell's presentation.
你就是在干这个
That's what you're doing?
我不敢相信你竟然背着我搞这样的事
I can't believe you would go behind my back.
我是为了咱俩的生意 我只是想得到那笔项目
Well, I'm doing it for us. I'm trying to get us this job.
我否决了
But I forbade it.
我觉得你错了
Well, I think you were wrong.
我们要不要投票
Should we vote on it?
你们要怎么投票 只有...
How're you gonna vote on it, there's only the...
别别别说了
Don't-Don't-Don't even.
你真是太固执己见了
Look, you're being pigheaded.
你来看一眼
Just take a look at it.
不用 我看得很明白
No. I've seen all I need to see.
接下来
Here's what's gonna happen:
我自己一个人给丽莎·麦卡弗里做演示
I'm gonna do the presentation to Lisa McCaffrey on my own,
不跟你还有你新死党一道
without you or your new best friend.
哦 是吗
Oh, really?
你非要固执己见 搞黄我们的生意吗
So, you're gonna be so stubborn that you ruin it for both of us?
没错 你要是想见她的话
Yes. And if you want a meeting with her,
你自己抽时间去帮她加鳄梨酱吧
you can go guac her taco on your own time.
好的 重点是 我是你的新死党
Okay, the headline is I'm your new best friend.
就算是唐 这反应有些偏激了
Wow, that sounds like a real overreaction, even for Don.
他就跟头驴一样倔
He is stubborn like a mule.
还跟驴一样 你要是在他后头走 他就踹你
Also like a mule, you can't walk up behind him or he'll kick you.
所以有两头驴在闹别扭咯
Uh-huh, so there are two mules in this fight.
等等 我为什么是驴
Wait, why am I a mule?
我跟你吵过多少次架了都 我的朋友
Oh, please, I have had many a fight with you, my friend.
你告诉我
What, you're telling me
对方提出了一个特别棒的观点
that you change your mind when you hear a good argument
你会改变注意吗
for the other point of view?
别人有了再说
Well, I'll let you know when I hear one.
很显然对于唐来说 这不仅仅是拿到一份工作
Look, obviously for Don, this is about more than getting a job.
有时候看起来是一回事
I mean, sometimes things seem like they're about one thing,
但其实不是那么一回事
but they're really about something else.
- 你这么觉得 - 嗯呐
- You think? - Yeah.
就像 罗德里格兹老师跟你做的春梦
Like... Mrs. Rodriguez had a sex dream about you.
这就是因为
That's got to be
另外一回事了
about something else.
啥
What?!
是你编出来的还是真的
Did you just make that example up or is that real?
就算是我编的...
Let's just say I made it up...
但货真价实
but it's real.
我在学校还得跟她碰面
I have to see her at school.
你干嘛跟我说这个
Why would you tell me that?
因为我想看看
Well, because I wanted to see
她告诉我的时候我是什么表情
what my face looked like when she told me.
所以 现在
So, you know...
我看到了
got it.
别介 光是唐的事
Come on, I already got
就把我搞得焦头烂额了
my hands full with Don.
好吧
Okay. I mean...
那你有没有想过
All right, well, did you even try to find out
唐到底在烦什么呢
what's really bothering Don?
再说一次 你不了解男人做事的方式
Once again, you have no concept of how men do things.
好吗 我们不讨论感受
Okay? We don't ask about feelings.
感受很久以前就被发明出来了
Feelings were invented a long time ago,
这样女人们才有饭后谈资
so that women would have something to talk about
在洞穴里待着
back at the cave...
而男人们外出狩猎
while men were out hunting.
好的
Okay.
好 那你有什么招
So, what's your plan?
我会用我一贯的风格
I'm gonna handle things with Don
跟唐解决好的
the way I always handle things with Don.
就是互相折磨互相伤害
By torturing and harassing each other
永远做不成什么事
and never accomplishing anything.
这就是传说中的"猫和老鼠"模式
Also known as the Tom-and-Jerry method.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
随你怎么说 这俩可是风靡一时的好莱坞明星
Say what you will, those two guys took Hollywood by storm.
我的椅子呢
Where's my chair?
你可以去移动公厕看看
You might want to look in the Porta Potti.
不行啊 因为我把移动公厕
Well, I can't because I had the Porta Potti
都堆到你门前了
towed to your front porch.
享受那酸爽吧
Enjoy the smell.
太幼稚了
That is so juvenile.
是啊
Yeah, well...
我抽屉里怎么全是布丁
My drawer is full of pudding.
留个惊喜 我做了相当多的布丁
I'm not gonna ruin the surprise, but I made a lot of pudding...
然后把它们放满了每个角落
and it's in a lot of places.
你真的觉得没有我的帮助你可以做这个报告吗
You really think you can do this presentation without my help?
为什么不可以 你还认为
Why not? You think you can
没有我的帮助你可以做这个报告呢
do the presentation without my help.
我可没这么说
That's not what I said.
对不起 我听不到你说话
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
我的耳朵朝的是另一个方向
My ears are facing the other direction.
好了 你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
我要去外面干活了
I'll be outside working.
你准备好道歉了就叫我
Call me when you're ready to apologize, huh?
我找到剩下的布丁了
I found the rest of the pudding.
你觉得就这些吗
Oh, you think so?
好了 快点 艾米
Okay, come on, Emme.
赶紧在罗德里格兹老师回来之前离开
Hurry up before Mrs. Rodriguez gets back.
你瞅啥
What are you looking at?
安迪告诉你了
Andi talk to you?
很不幸 是的
Unfortunately, yes.
现在我没那么冷血了 是吧
I'm not ice-cold now, am I?
我们以后得让你搭顺风车回家了
We have got to get you in a carpool.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
我收到你发的电子邮件
I got an e-mail from you
说你想道歉
saying you wanted to apologize.
我们来听听 然后我好拒绝你
Let's hear it so I can say no.
我没给你发邮件 你个大狒狒
I didn't e-mail you, you big baboon.
还是我真发了
Or did I?
你把手机落在这里了
You leave your phone out,
美好的事情便发生了
beautiful things happen.
如果他不道歉的话
Well, I'm not gonna stay here
我是不会呆在这里的
if he's not gonna apologize.
我是不会道歉的
Well, I'm not apologizing.
好了 猫鼠游戏到此为止
Okay, all right, Tom and Jerry, that's it.
现在由我来做主 坐下 坐下
I am in charge now. Sit down. Sit down.
好了 显然问题越陷越深了
Okay, now, obviously something deeper is going on here,
我们找找根源
and we need to get to the bottom of it.
唐 你说说你为什么生亚当的气
Now, Don, why are you so mad at Adam?
因为他是个蛮横的老板 他总是这样
Because he's a bossy boss and he's always a bossy boss.
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
我听到的是 唐觉得
Um, and what I'm hearing is that, uh, Don feels like
你从来不听他的想法
you don't listen to him and his ideas.
净说瞎话
That's a bunch of crap.
好了
Okay.
我觉得亚当是说
I-I-I think what Adam is saying is
他不知道你是这么想的
he never knew you felt that way.
我是哥哥
I'm the older brother.
有点意思
Interesting.
好了
Okay, um,
我觉得唐是说 照道理
I-I-I think what Don is saying is that traditionally,
他应该是你们二人的领导者
he would be the leader in your relationship.
好吧 也许他年长 但是他就是个巨婴
Okay, he may be older, but he's a big baby.
好了
Okay.
我觉得亚当是说
Um, I think what-what Adam is saying
有时候他觉得你不会为了生意做最好的选择
is that sometimes he feels like you don't do what's best
不当彼此是平等的合作伙伴
for the business, like an equal partner.
他从来没把我当做平等的合作伙伴对待
He's never treated me like an equal partner.
你是因为觉得对我有愧
You only asked me to start the business with you
才跟我一起做生意
because you felt sorry for me.
- 什么 - 好了 等一下
- What?  - Okay, okay, w-wait.
我觉得唐是说...
I think what Don is saying is...
我觉得他说的挺好的
Oh... oh, I think he actually said it.
我只是你那个不能自己处理问题的傻大哥
I'm just your big, dumb brother who couldn't make it on his own.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
我让你跟我一起做生意是因为我需要你
I asked you to do it because I needed you,
但你总是一副帮了我大忙的样子
and you've always acted like you were doing me a big favor.
我在升华自我
I was sublimating.
是的 我看你那个无聊透顶的每日一词日历了
Yeah, I read that stupid word-of-the-day calendar.
谢谢你 让我忘掉了365个绝好的单词
Thanks to you, I forgot 365 perfectly good words.
听着 没有你 伯恩斯兄弟什么都不是
Look, without you, Burns Brothers would be nothing.
我不能像你一样跟别人谈成生意
I can't talk to people and close deals like you can.
你是我们的秘密武器
You're our secret weapon.
那是必须的
You bet your ass I am.
当你喜欢洛厄尔做的东西时
And when you liked Lowell's thing,
我以为你要找别人来取代我
I thought you were trying to find someone to replace me.
你是我的哥哥
You're my brother.
我就算是想也不可能摆脱你啊
I couldn't get rid of you even if I wanted to.
我觉得亚当是说他爱你
I think what Adam is saying is he loves you.
什么 不不 我没说
What? N-N-No, I'm not. No.
太好了 如果你那么说我就扁你
Well, good, 'cause I would've kicked your ass.
噢 他也爱你
Aw, he loves you, too.
好了 听着
All right, look,
如果你不想用洛厄尔的东西作报告
if you want to do the presentation without Lowell
我无所谓
that's fine with me.
我宁可丢了工作
I-I-I'd rather lose the job
也不想丢了哥哥
than lose my brother.
我用洛厄尔倒是没问题 只要我们一起做就行
Well, I'm fine using Lowell, as long as we do it together.
很好
Good.
那么我们去你的门移动公厕搬走吧
Okay, so, let's go get that Porta Potti off your porch.
这活可真够脏的
That's gonna be a filthy job.
她是这么说的
That's what she said.
- 嘿 亲爱的 - 嘿
- Hey, honey. - Hey.
报告做得怎么样
How was the presentation?
我们把所有人赢的落花流水
Oh, we blew everyone out of the water.
所以 想象一下当她把工作给了
So, imagine our surprise when she gave the job to her nephew
她刚被百思买炒掉的侄子时 我们有多惊讶
who just got fired from Best Buy.
亲爱的 真遗憾
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
是啊 但是她正在建的迷你商城
Yeah, but the mini-mall she's building
被伯恩斯兄弟建筑拿下了
is going to Burns Brothers Construction.
天啊 这太棒了
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
是啊 她的侄子在建房子的时候就会受罪了
Yeah, that nephew's gonna have a hard time building houses
因为他的手套里全是布丁
when he keeps finding pudding in his gloves.
猜猜谁将会给这些人
And guess who's gonna build
建网站 是我
a website for these guys? Me.
你不用猜了 我只是想说出来
You don't have to guess, I just wanted to say it.
是啊 如果不是你把我们和洛厄尔联系起来
Yeah, and none of it would've happened
让我和唐重归于好
if you hadn't put us together with Lowell,
这一切都不会发生
and put me and Don back together.
所以... 谢谢你的多管闲事
So... thanks for not staying out of stuff.
跟高兴跟你一起干活
Pleasure doing business with you.
她是这么说的
That's what she said.
安迪撤了
Andi out.
这梗不错
Now that one was solid. Huh?
我的宝贝在这呢
There's my girl.
安迪 安迪
Ugh, Andi. Andi.
我刚做了一个特诡异的梦
I just had the weirdest dream.
啪啪啪 伯恩斯先生
Boom-chucka-chucka, Mr. Burns.
算了 我心脏可受不了再来一下了
Oh, forget it. My heart can't take another one.
匹兹堡的一支冰球队
Little Debbie 麦基食品旗下子品牌
Cinemax频道会在深夜播放色情电影